Finding Aid for Angela Morgan Papers 1861-1957
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Poems
  - Ogontz Meals, 1939 (Box 33)
  - Oh, How I Bless the Sun (Box 33)
  - Oh, Mothers, Mothers, Mothers (Box 33)
  - Oh, What A Sky, 1905 (Box 33)
  - Oh, Who Can Sense the Rapture of the Trees, 1919 (Box 33)
  - Oh, Why Not Love (Box 33)
  - Old Order (Box 33)
  - Old Pharaoh (Box 33)
  - On the Just and the Unjust, 1929 (Box 33)
  - On Visiting the Hothouses in Holland (Box 33)
  - Once I Saw a Woman's Eyes (Box 33)
  - Once to Every Man and Nation, 1922 (Box 33)
  - Once Upon a Time I Was Just Myself, 1938 (Box 33)
  - One Only (Box 33)
  - Open the Gates (Box 33)
  - Opening of Parliament, 1924 (Box 33)
  - Optimist's View, 1919 (Box 33)
  - Oranges, 1940 (Box 33)
  - Orchid Dusk (Box 33)
  - Our Daily Bread (Box 33)
  - Our Drive Through Modena, 1935 (Box 33)
  - Out of the Stony Ground, 1934 (Box 33)
  - Outer Shape of An Event, 1924 (Box 33)
  - Overlord, 1922 (Box 33)
  - Ownership (Box 33)
  - Pain of Love, 1922 (Box 33)
  - Paintin' Blinds, 1930 (Box 33)
  - Pan American Hymn (Box 33)
  - Parkway Fountain (Box 33)
  - Parson's Wife, 1922 (Box 33)
  - Passport (Box 33)
  - Pasteboard Box, 1918 (Box 33)
  - Path He Chose, 1922 (Box 33)
  - Pause! Watch Your Pulse Beat, 1936 (Box 33)
  - Peace Can Be No Better, 1945 (Box 33)
  - Peaches (Box 33)
  - Pentecostal Hymn, 1930 (Box 33)
  - People and Friends, 1953 (Box 33)
  - People Keep Right on Marrying, 1936 (Box 33)
  - People Who Budget (Box 33)
  - Personality, 1922 (Box 33)
  - Petals, 1922 (Box 33)
  - Petition (Box 33)
  - Philosophy in a Grocery Store, 1922 (Box 33)
  - Picture, 1932 (Box 33)
  - Pictured in Silence (Box 33)
  - Pictures in Summer, 1920 (Box 33)
  - Pioneer Woman, 1953 (Box 33)
  - Place of Understanding, 1919 (Box 33)
  - Play (Box 33)
  - Plea of the Child, 1915 (Box 33)
  - Pledges (Box 33)
  - Poet (Box 33)
  - Poetry in the Dictionary, 1923 (Box 33)
  - Poetry Was Not Made for Drawing Rooms (Box 33)
  - Poets of Today (Box 33)
  - Pools (Box 34)
  - Pools of Paradise, 1921 (Box 34)
  - Poplars in the Wind, 1920 (Box 34)
  - Portrait (Box 34)
  - Potatoes, 1921 (Box 34)
  - Povla Frijsh (Box 34)
  - Power, 1927 (Box 34)
  - Power, 1934 (Box 34)
  - Power to Earn, 1924 (Box 34)
  - Praise in July, 1935 (Box 34)
  - Prayer for Rain (Box 34)
  - Prayer for the Imbecile World (Box 34)
  - Prayer in Spring (Box 34)
  - Prayer to the Unknown Soldier, 1931 (Box 34)
  - Presence, 1914 (Box 34)
  - Prime of Life (Box 34)
  - Prince Goes By, 1929 (Box 34)
  - Prince of Peace, 1923 (Box 34)
  - Princess in Disguise (Box 34)
  - Prisms in the Palm Court (Box 34)
  - Privacy (Box 34)
  - Progress, 1921 (Box 34)
  - Prophet, 1911 (Box 34)
  - Prosperity, 1923 (Box 34)
  - Psycho-Analysis, 1922 (Box 34)
  - Queen Mother, 1952 (Box 34)
  - Queen Remembers, 1936 (Box 34)
  - Queens Are Made in Paradise (Box 34)
  - Questions in Spring (Box 34)
  - Rabbit Show (Box 34)
  - Radar (Box 34)
  - Radio, 1924 (Box 34)
  - Rain Has Made A Curtain, 1922 (Box 34)
  - Rainbow Girlhood (Box 34)
  - Rainy Streets, 1921 (Box 34)
  - Ramsay MacDonald, 1924 (Box 34)
  - Real People (Box 34)
  - Reality, 1901 (Box 34)
  - Reason, 1912 (Box 34)
  - Reconciliation (Box 34)
  - Red Legislation, 1924 (Box 34)
  - Red Spirited, 1920 (Box 34)
  - Redwoods (Box 34)
  - Regret, 1923 (Box 34)
  - Remembered (Box 34)
  - Rend the Atom (Box 34)
  - Request, 1935 (Box 34)
  - Resurgam, 1926 (Box 34)
  - Resurrection, 1910 (Box 34)
  - Reunion, 1933 (Box 34)
  - Reunion, 1940 (Box 34)
  - Revelation, 1936 (Box 34)
  - Revolt (Box 34)
  - Revolt in Spring (Box 34)
  - Rewards, 1927 (Box 34)
  - Rhymes of Unruly Things, 1920 (Box 34)
  - Rhythm of Legs (Box 34)
  - Rhythm of Your Body, 1952 (Box 34)
  - Ribbon and Twine (Box 34)
  - Rich Autumn in Near, 1935 (Box 34)
  - Rich Man, Poor Man (Box 34)
  - Riches (Box 34)
  - Riches and Relief, 1932 (Box 34)
  - Rider of the Elements (Box 34)
  - Riders of the Moon (Box 34)
  - Right of Way, 1925 (Box 34)
  - Right to Room (Box 34)
  - Ring Night, 1928 (Box 34)
  - Ringing True, 1922 (Box 34)
  - Ripening, 1922 (Box 34)
  - Robert Logan (Box 34)
  - Robert Norwood (Box 34)
  - Rocky Mountain Blue Jay, 1937 (Box 34)
  - Roof Tenants, 1918 (Box 34)
  - Room, 1913 (Box 34)
  - Roosevelt, 1924 (Box 34)
  - Rose, 1916 (Box 34)
  - Rose Fire, 1923 (Box 34)
  - Runaway Gold (Box 34)
  - Sacred Book, 1940 (Box 34)
  - Saints of Latter Days, 1952 (Box 34)
  - Samson Has the Temple, 1921 (Box 34)
  - Samuel Fleischer, 1929 (Box 34)
  - Sanctuary, 1930 (Box 34)
  - Saviors of Earth (Box 34)
  - Saviours, 1918 (Box 34)
  - Say I Love, 1921 (Box 34)
  - Say I Will (Box 34)
  - Say You Are Glad, 1922 (Box 34)
  - Scarlet Sin, 1920 (Box 34)
  - Scars, 1922 (Box 34)
  - Science or Symphony, 1922 (Box 34)
  - Science Shelf (Box 34)
  - Sculptor Speaks, 1922 (Box 34)
  - Sea Dark Night (Box 34)
  - Sea Gull (Box 34)
  - Sea Gulls and Ferry Boats (Box 34)
  - Second Coming, 1923 (Box 34)
  - Secret of the Moon, 1920 (Box 34)
  - Secret of the Rose, 1922 (Box 34)
  - Seeds of Sand (Box 34)
  - Seeing Above, 1931 (Box 34)
  - Seiberling, 1931 (Box 34)
  - Self Rides On (Box 34)
  - Self Supreme, 1920 (Box 34)
  - Sentimentalist, 1922 (Box 34)
  - Shadows, 1925 (Box 34)
  - Shakespeare of Tibet (Box 34)
  - Shall We Remember (Box 34)
  - Shame (Box 34)
  - Shawl of Radiance, 1937 (Box 34)
  - She Who Gave All, 1922 (Box 34)
  - Ships of Love, 1925 (Box 34)
  - Shoes in the Morning (Box 34)
  - Signals, 1920 (Box 34)
  - Signs and Wonders, 1926 (Box 34)
  - Silence, 1927 (Box 34)
  - Silver and Gold (Box 34)
  - Silver Clothes, 1925 (Box 34)
  - Silver Deluge (Box 34)
  - Silver Epic (Box 34)
  - Silver-Silver, 1936 (Box 34)
  - Singing Heaven, 1937 (Box 34)
  - Singing Rafters, 1930 (Box 34)
  - Singing World-Shining Substance (Box 34)
  - Sin or Song, 1932 (Box 34)
  - Sir Galahad (Box 34)
  - Sister Dear, Sister Dear (Box 34)
  - Sketches in Autumn (Box 34)
  - Sketches in White (Box 34)
  - Sky, 1920 (Box 34)
  - Sky Bubbles (Box 34)
  - Skyscraper, 1922 (Box 34)
  - Sleep, 1923 (Box 34)
  - Sleep Gardens, 1915 (Box 34)
  - Sleep the Restorer (Box 34)
  - Sleeping and Waking, 1935 (Box 34)
  - Slumber, 1922 (Box 34)
  - Smile (Box 34)
  - Snow Drift (Box 34)
  - Snow Sky (Box 34)
  - Snow on the Pines (Box 34)
  - Snow Storm, 1939 (Box 34)
  - So Much Has Come Between, 1922 (Box 34)
  - Soap Dish Philosophy, 1922 (Box 34)
  - Some Folks Say We Can't Remember (Box 34)
  - Someone Said God Bless, 1940 (Box 34)
  - Something From Above Comes Down, 1929 (Box 34)
  - Son In Your Arms, 1949 (Box 34)
  - Son Is Born (Box 34)
  - Song In Summer, 1936 (Box 34)
  - Song of a Good Hot Meal, 1922 (Box 34)
  - Song of Better Times, 1920 (Box 34)
  - Song of Flowing Gold, 1930 (Box 34)
  - Song of Freedom, 1946 (Box 34)
  - Song of Gratitude, 1931 (Box 34)
  - Song of Hope, 1943 (Box 34)
  - Song of Housework (Box 34)
  - Song of Jewels (Box 34)
  - Song of Life, 1911 (Box 34)
  - Song of Manhattan, 1921 (Box 34)
  - Song of New Days, 1921 (Box 34)
  - Song of Praise, 1912 (Box 34)
  - Song of Summer, 1936 (Box 34)
  - Song of Summer Days, 1922 (Box 34)
  - Song of Tender Things, 1918 (Box 35)
  - Song of Thanks, 1912 (Box 35)
  - Song of Thanksgiving, 1912 (Box 35)
  - Song of the Backslider (Box 35)
  - Song of the Clothes Hangers (Box 35)
  - Song of the New World, 1920 (Box 35)
  - Song of the Seeds, 1926 (Box 35)
  - Song of the Senses (Box 35)
  - Song of the Wheat, 1929 (Box 35)
  - Song That's Older than Rome (Box 35)
  - Songs of the Body, 1922 (Box 35)
  - Sonnet to One Recovered, 1930 (Box 35)
  - Sonnet to Secrecy (Box 35)
  - Soon After Dark, 1923 (Box 35)
  - Sorting (Box 35)
  - Soul of India, 1952 (Box 35)
  - Soul of the City (Box 35)
  - Space Daughter, 1953 (Box 35)
  - Speak to me with Eyes of Love, 1918 (Box 35)
  - Spirit of William Penn, 1941 (Box 35)
  - Splendid Story, 1953 (Box 35)
  - Spoken Word, 1934 (Box 35)
  - Spooning (Box 35)
  - Spring Fever, 1939 (Box 35)
  - Spring Flood (Box 35)
  - Spring in Kensington Gardens (Box 35)
  - Spring Landscape in Rain, 1934 (Box 35)
  - Spring Passed Over My Spirit (Box 35)
  - Spring Song (Box 35)
  - Spring Trees in Town, 1923 (Box 35)
  - Springtime Ditty (Box 35)
  - Stand and Deliver, 1922 (Box 35)
  - Stand Forth, 1915 (Box 35)
  - Star, 1919 (Box 35)
  - Star Comfort, 1923 (Box 35)
  - Star Dripping Tree, 1934 (Box 35)
  - Star in the East (Box 35)
  - Stars (Box 35)
  - Stars and Dahlias (Box 35)
  - Starshine Lady, 1938 (Box 35)
  - Statement of Faith (Box 35)
  - Stone, 1928 (Box 35)
  - Stones, 1929 (Box 35)
  - Storm (Box 35)
  - Storm Celestial, 1926 (Box 35)
  - Storm of Glory (Box 35)
  - Stowaway, 1922 (Box 35)
  - Strange Lover (Box 35)
  - Strange Mana (Box 35)
  - Stranger (Box 35)
  - Strip of Star Light (Box 35)
  - Subconscious (Box 35)
  - Sublimation (Box 35)
  - Sudden a Sea-Gull, 1922 (Box 35)
  - Sudden Love (Box 35)
  - Suddenly They Saw (Box 35)
  - Summer Vacation (Box 35)
  - Summit (Box 35)
  - Summons, 1916 (Box 35)
  - Summons, 1938 (Box 35)
  - Summum Bonum (Box 35)
  - Sun in Our Eyes, 1924 (Box 35)
  - Sun on the Floor, 1937 (Box 35)
  - Sundown, 1923 (Box 35)
  - Sunlight in London, 1924 (Box 35)
  - Sunset (Box 35)
  - Sunshine Come to Me, 1942 (Box 35)
  - Super Mother, 1929 (Box 35)
  - Suppose, 1918 (Box 35)
  - Supremacy (Box 35)
  - Sweet is the Hillside, 1929 (Box 35)
  - Swimming Lesson (Box 35)
  - Swing Out My Soul (Box 35)
  - Swing Song of the Sphere, 1939 (Box 35)
  - Symphony Leader, 1938 (Box 35)
  - Tall Alladin (Box 35)
  - Tapestry (Box 35)
  - Taste of Apples, 1938 (Box 35)
  - Tea (Box 35)
  - Teacher, 1926 (Box 35)
  - Teacher of Men (Box 35)
  - Tears, 1923 (Box 35)
  - Tell Me Trees of Avon, 1923 (Box 35)
  - Temptation (Box 35)
  - Terrible Ones (Box 35)
  - Test of Friendship, 1923 (Box 35)
  - Thanksgiving, 1911 (Box 35)
  - Thanksgiving in Summer (Box 35)
  - That Starry Person (Box 35)
  - Thaw (Box 35)
  - Then Flashed a Humming Bird (Box 35)
  - There Is No Time (Box 35)
  - There Must Be Love (Box 35)
  - There's A Girl In My Heart, 1952 (Box 35)
  - There's Always Something Else to Wash, 1929 (Box 35)
  - These People (Box 35)
  - They Toil Not, 1937 (Box 35)
  - There Were There All of the Time, 1934 (Box 35)
  - Things Have Made a Path for You, 1940 (Box 35)
  - Things I Remember, 1920 (Box 35)
  - Think of Me Honey (Box 35)
  - This Age a Temple Seems (Box 35)
  - This Hour (Box 35)
  - This Is America (Box 35)
  - This Is Love, This Is Light, 1953 (Box 35)
  - This Is the Kind of Love (Box 35)
  - This Precious Thing (Box 35)
  - This To Me Is Life, 1922 (Box 35)
  - Thistledown, 1928 (Box 35)
  - Thou Hast Uttered Me (Box 35)
  - Three Green Trees, 1942 (Box 35)
  - Three Women, 1921 (Box 35)
  - Thwarted Souls (Box 35)
  - Tidings Triumphant, 1916 (Box 35)
  - Tight-Rope World, 1926 (Box 35)
  - Time, 1924 (Box 35)
  - Time and Eternity, 1939 (Box 35)
  - Time for Love Has Come, 1940 (Box 35)
  - Time, Mirror of Eternity, 1951 (Box 35)
  - Ting-a-ling, 1938 (Box 35)
  - Titan, 1916 (Box 35)
  - To A Bride, 1922 (Box 35)
  - To A Bride's Mother (Box 35)
  - To A Heedless Daughter, 1920 (Box 35)
  - To A Lady's Ankles (Box 35)
  - To A Mother Gone (Box 35)
  - To A New Born Infant (Box 35)
  - To A Newly Planted Field At Night, 1922 (Box 35)
  - To A Pair of Old Shoes, 1922 (Box 35)
  - To A Railroad Train At Night, 1921 (Box 35)
  - To A Song Bird, 1929 (Box 35)
  - To A Tree in June, 1920 (Box 35)
  - To A Violin, 1922 (Box 35)
  - To A Woman Knitting, 1920 (Box 35)
  - To Adlai Stevenson, 1952 (Box 35)
  - To Amelia Earhart (Box 35)
  - To America, 1915 (Box 35)
  - To An April Bud, 1919 (Box 35)
  - To An Autumn Tree in the Sun (Box 35)
  - To An Unknown In the Omnibus, 1926 (Box 35)
  - To And Fro, 1926 (Box 35)
  - To Arthur Mees, 1923 (Box 35)
  - To Abdul Baha, 1929 (Box 35)
  - To Be Alive In Such An Age, 1915 (Box 35)
  - To Charles Wagner (Box 35)
  - To David Windsor (Box 35)
  - To Dee Shaw (Box 35)
  - To Edgar Allan Poe, 1934 (Box 35)
  - To Edwin Markham (Box 35)
  - To Ella Myer (Box 35)
  - To Emmy Lou's Photograph (Box 35)
  - To Eugene Debs, 1921 (Box 35)
  - To Fenwicke Holmes (Box 35)
  - To Frederick B. Fisher (Box 35)
  - To Gertrude's Cats (Box 35)
  - To Helen Hunter (Box 35)
  - To Helen Temple Cooke (Box 35)
  - To Irene Harrison (Box 35)
  - To Jane Addams (Box 35)
  - To Jean (Box 35)
  - To Kay Agar, 1934 (Box 35)
  - To Lady Astor, 1922 (Box 35)
  - To Madame Curie (Box 35)
  - To Meredith (Box 35)
  - To Mrs. Kate Crane Gartz, 1941 (Box 35)
  - To My Mother on Mother's Day, 1934 (Box 35)
  - To One Who Does Not Know I Love Him (Box 35)
  - To Poets in Ivory Towers, 1940 (Box 36)
  - To Prepare a Place, 1926 (Box 36)
  - To the Bride (Box 36)
  - To The Dining Car Passengers (Box 36)
  - To The Disheartened, 1919 (Box 36)
  - To The Girl Scouts of America (Box 36)
  - To the Power Unseen (Box 36)
  - To the Thurbers, 1939 (Box 36)
  - To The Unappreciated, 1951 (Box 36)
  - To Those Who Love Him (Box 36)
  - To Vi (Box 36)
  - To Wealthy Honsinger Fisher (Box 36)
  - To Will Rogers (Box 36)
  - Toast (Box 36)
  - Today, 1912 (Box 36)
  - Today A Dream Has Come True, 1936 (Box 36)
  - Today Is Resurrection (Box 36)
  - Today's Gospel (Box 36)
  - Tombs and Effigies, 1929 (Box 36)
  - Tombs of Antiquity (Box 36)
  - Top of the Stairs (Box 36)
  - Torch of the World, 1918, 2 folders (Box 36)
  - Torn Letter, 1923 (Box 36)
  - Tower of Evening, 1937 (Box 36)
  - Transfiguration (Box 36)
  - Transfusion, 1938 (Box 36)
  - Travail (Box 36)
  - Travesty (Box 36)
  - Tree, 1923 (Box 36)
  - Tree of Transfiguration (Box 36)
  - Tree People, 1923 (Box 36)
  - Tree Trunks, 1939 (Box 36)
  - Trees (Box 36)
  - Trees Are Astronomers, 1919 (Box 36)
  - Trees Are Radio Stations (Box 36)
  - Tree At Night (Box 36)
  - Trees In Spring (Box 36)
  - Trees of Marietta (Box 36)
  - Trees Saw Me Coming (Box 36)
  - Trees That Died In the War, 1926 (Box 36)
  - Tribute (Box 36)
  - Tribute to Abby A. Sutherland (Box 36)
  - Tribute to Bonesteel's, 1950 (Box 36)
  - Tribute to Frank Laubach (Box 36)
  - Tribute to Greatness, 1919 (Box 36)
  - Tribute to James M. Anders (Box 36)
  - Triumphant Ascent (Box 36)
  - Trumpets of Tut-Ankhamen (Box 36)
  - Truth Triumphant (Box 36)
  - Try It, 1918 (Box 36)
  - Tulip Beds in Holland (Box 36)
  - Tune Up to Joy (Box 36)
  - Twenty A Week (Box 36)
  - Two Men (Box 36)
  - Two Talk of Dawn (Box 36)
  - Two Views of Sacrifice, 1920 (Box 36)
  - Unattainable (Box 36)
  - Underprivileged (Box 36)
  - United Nations Hymn, 1947 (Box 36)
  - Unity, 1926 (Box 36)
  - Unknown Soldier, 1921 (Box 36)
  - Up There, 1923 (Box 36)
  - Upward Going Things (Box 36)
  - Utterance, 1916 (Box 36)
  - Vacuum Cleaner (Box 36)
  - Valentine Poems, 1935 (Box 36)
  - Vanity, 1930 (Box 36)
  - Vast (Box 36)
  - Veils (Box 36)
  - Venus From the Back Yard Fence, 1941 (Box 36)
  - Vermont, 1930 (Box 36)
  - Verse or Two on Jim (Box 36)
  - Victory Hymn (Box 36)
  - Viewpoint (Box 36)
  - Vigorously I Tell It, 1938 (Box 36)
  - Vindication (Box 36)
  - Virginity, 1921 (Box 36)
  - Vision Perfect, 1921 (Box 36)
  - Voice of My Lover, 1915 (Box 36)
  - Voice of the Child (Box 36)
  - Waking Time (Box 36)
  - Walking Like Satin, 1941 (Box 36)
  - Wall, 1921 (Box 36)
  - Walls, 1929 (Box 36)
  - War In The Clouds, 1939 (Box 36)
  - War Time (Box 36)
  - Warm Up, 1928 (Box 36)
  - Wasp (Box 36)
  - Water, 1921 (Box 36)
  - We Meet Again Beneath the Trees, 1940 (Box 36)
  - We Too Had Dreams (Box 36)
  - Wealth Of God (Box 36)
  - Wembley, 1924 (Box 36)
  - What Do I Wish For You, 1925 (Box 36)
  - What Have Ye Done, 1914 (Box 36)
  - What Is My Wisdom, 1919 (Box 36)
  - What of my Boredom (Box 36)
  - What Poetry Means to Me (Box 36)
  - What the Snow Does to Our Landscape, 1936 (Box 36)
  - What Will Remove Rust, 1939 (Box 36)
  - What Word, 1913 (Box 36)
  - What's In a Name (Box 36)
  - When I Am Tired, 1933 (Box 36)
  - When I Go Forth (Box 36)
  - When Mother's Baking Bread (Box 36)
  - When Nature Wants A Man, 1918 (Box 36)
  - When People Sing (Box 36)
  - When the Blaze Lets Go (Box 36)
  - Where Art May Grow, 1926 (Box 36)
  - Where Is the Mirror (Box 36)
  - Where Stars Are Born, 1920 (Box 36)
  - Where Your Treasure Is, 1935 (Box 36)
  - Which of These Three (Box 36)
  - Whirlwind Vision (Box 36)
  - White Slave (Box 36)
  - White Winds (Box 36)
  - Whizz and Whine (Box 36)
  - Who Are The Criminals (Box 36)
  - Who Saw, 1929 (Box 36)
  - Who Shall Sing (Box 36)
  - Whole Year Christmas, 1913 (Box 36)
  - Why, 1919 (Box 36)
  - Why Are Your Hands Cold, 1953 (Box 36)
  - Why God Made Girls, 1927 (Box 36)
  - Why Not Invest in People, 1937 (Box 36)
  - Why Tarry, Why Wait, 1949 (Box 36)
  - Why This Haste (Box 36)
  - Why Wasn't I There (Box 36)
  - Why Winter Comes (Box 36)
  - Wild Prophecy, 1935 (Box 36)
  - Wind Bloweth, 1929 (Box 36)
  - Window Panes (Box 36)
  - Winged Victors, 1919 (Box 36)
  - Wings for the Lame (Box 36)
  - Wings of the Sod (Box 36)
  - Winter (Box 36)
  - Winter Sport (Box 36)
  - Winter Sunset (Box 36)
  - Winter Tree Trunks, 1939 (Box 36)
  - Winter Trees (Box 36)
  - Wishes, 1938 (Box 36)
  - Wishes At Dawn, 1921 (Box 36)
  - With His Own Hands (Box 36)
  - Without Cherubim (Box 36)
  - Without the Taking Away of Love (Box 36)
  - Wizardry, 1926 (Box 36)
  - Woman (Box 36)
  - Woman Beloved, 1928 (Box 36)
  - Woman Darning (Box 36)
  - Woman I Know (Box 36)
  - Woman of Light (Box 36)
  - Woman the Mystery, 1930 (Box 36)
  - Women and Children First, 1913 (Box 36)
  - Women Come Out, 1920 (Box 36)
  - Women Who Knit and Sew (Box 36)
  - Women's Foolish Feet, 1923 (Box 36)
  - Wonder, 1922 (Box 36)
  - Wonder of Sleep, 1922 (Box 36)
  - Wood Hath A Soul, 1918 (Box 36)
  - Wood Made Flesh and Bones (Box 36)
  - Wood Smoke (Box 37)
  - Woodman's Love, 1923 (Box 37)
  - Word (Box 37)
  - Work, A Song of Triumph, 1916, 2 folders (Box 37)
  - Workmen's Song (Box 37)
  - World Is A Wonderful Place, 1936 (Box 37)
  - World Of Tomorrow (Box 37)
  - Would I Could Enter (Box 37)
  - Would I Like to be A Man, 1953 (Box 37)
  - Yellow Roses, 1918 (Box 37)
  - Yoga, 1938 (Box 37)
  - You (Box 37)
  - You Are the Miracle (Box 37)
  - You Ask Me Why, 1938 (Box 37)
  - You Have Come Back, 1918 (Box 37)
  - You Have Forgotten (Box 37)
  - You Left Me Free, 1922 (Box 37)
  - You Said I Would Forget, 1920 (Box 37)
  - Young Husband to his Wife (Box 37)
  - Your Better Self, 1923 (Box 37)
  - Your Coming, 1912 (Box 37)
  - Your Neighbor's Happiness (Box 37)
  - Youth, 1922 (Box 37)
  - Youth Beware (Box 37)
  - Youth Everlasting (Box 37)
  - Youth to his Maiden (Box 37)
  - Zippers, 1953 (Box 37)
  - Complete List of Poems by Angela Morgan 1916 (Box 37)
  - Miscellaneous and A-L (Box 59)
  - M-W (Box 59)
- Short Stories, Articles and Essays
  The series Short Stories, Articles and Essays consists of published and unpublished works by Angela Morgan. It is arranged alphabetically by title. Drafts and ideas for stories, articles and essays are also found in the Manuscripts and Drafts series (boxes 50-58).
  - Artists as Civilization Builders (Box 37)
  - As Regards a Thesaurus (Box 37)
  - As to Poetry 1951 (Box 37)
  - At the Call of Josephine (Box 37)
  - Beauty and Bread 1926 (Box 37)
  - Book Reviews by Angela Morgan (Box 37)
  - Boston Training School for Wives (Box 37)
  - Briarcliff Race (Box 37)
  - Can People be Made to Love Poetry 1932, 3 folders (Box 37)
  - Can Poets Thrive in a War-Made World (Box 37)
  - Can We Really Make Christmas Come True (Box 37)
  - Challenge of This Age 1936 (Box 37)
  - Charles Aked Interview (Box 37)
  - Covenant Fire (Box 37)
  - Creative Optimism (Box 37)
  - Crossed Wires (Box 37)
  - Deceitfulness of Riches (Box 37)
  - Delicatessen Lady (Box 37)
  - Do You Take This Man (Box 37)
  - Does Business Need Poetry (Box 37)
  - Don't Let the Whirlpool Get You (Box 37)
  - Drafts of Short Stories 1931 (Box 37)
  - Draw a Deep Breath (Box 37)
  - Drink (Box 37)
  - English General Strike Articles 1926 (Box 37)
  - Feelers of the Mind (Box 37)
  - Fourth Dimensional Wife, 5 folders (Box 37)
  - General Booth Interview (Box 37)
  - Glamour that is England (Box 37)
  - Grace Brown (Box 37)
  - Grace Carroll, Refined Specialty (Box 37)
  - Grant's Tomb (Box 37)
  - Gray's Churchyard 1925 (Box 37)
  - Great Men Who Have Missed Love (Box 37)
  - Great Upheaval 1926 (Box 37)
  - Heart of a Clod (Box 37)
  - Housewife (Box 37)
  - How Shall We Honor Poushkin (Box 37)
  - How the World Looks to a Poet (Box 37)
  - Humanity Must Take the Air (Box 37)
  - I Have Something to Say to You (Box 37)
  - If Abraham Lincoln (Box 37)
  - I'm in Love With Myself (Box 37)
  - In Search of Magic (Box 37)
  - Incorrigible Bachelor 1919 (Box 37)
  - Is a Wife's First Duty to her Husband or her Children (Box 37)
  - Is There a New Answer 1938, 2 folders (Box 37)
  - Julia Chandler Interview (Box 37)
  - Let's Talk It Over (Box 37)
  - Love Articles (Box 37)
  - Love Does Not Last (Box 38)
  - Love of Lida (Box 38)
  - Madame President, 4 folders (Box 38)
  - Make America Safe for Art 1928 (Box 38)
  - Man, a Girl and an Idea (Box 38)
  - Men in Mary's Life (Box 38)
  - Miss Vane 1911 (Box 38)
  - Mr. Charles (Box 38)
  - Mrs. Cassidente (Box 38)
  - Mrs. Stuyvesant Fish Interview, 2 folders (Box 38)
  - Monkey and Mercury (Box 38)
  - Moving Picture Articles (Box 38)
  - Mutiny (Box 38)
  - Now Is the Time (Box 38)
  - Of Royal Parentage 1920 (Box 38)
  - One Who Bore Them (Box 38)
  - Oscar Hammerstein Interview (Box 38)
  - Pay the Poet 1939 (Box 38)
  - Plunge Into Life (Box 38)
  - Poe Was a Stream of Molten Metal 1934 (Box 38)
  - Poetry and the War (Box 38)
  - Poetry of the Year (Box 38)
  - Point of Difference (Box 38)
  - Praise in July (Box 38)
  - Princess of the Sky (Box 38)
  - Puppies and Kittens in the Sun 1931 (Box 38)
  - Queer People of this Queer World (Box 38)
  - Ralph Peters Interview (Box 38)
  - Real Angels 1926 (Box 38)
  - Real Tragedy 1925 (Box 38)
  - Revaluation (Box 38)
  - Rose Livingston Interview on the White Slave Traffic (Box 38)
  - Shine Back at Them (Box 38)
  - Speed Up to God (Box 38)
  - Tainted Money (Box 38)
  - This Is the Story (Box 38)
  - This Radiant World (Box 38)
  - Thy Neighbor's Dream 1926 (Box 38)
  - Tramps at Your Door (Box 38)
  - Vital Things of Chatauqua 1916 (Box 38)
  - Way of Victory (Box 38)
  - What Do You Want (Box 38)
  - What is Interesting, 2 folders (Box 38)
  - What is Irksome (Box 38)
  - What Religion Means to Me (Box 38)
  - What Shall We Do With Mother, 10 folders (Box 38)
  - When the Woman Invites (Box 38)
  - Who Is Most Important (Box 38)
  - Whose Domain (Box 38)
  - Why Women Are Not So Well Read as Men 1924 (Box 38)
  - William G. McAdoo Interview (Box 38)
  - World Needs Quickening (Box 38)
  - Would You Like to Succeed as She Has Done (Box 38)
  - X-Ray Mind (Box 38)
  - "Baffle the Bully" (Box 59)
  - "The Highbrow" (Box 59)
- Manuscripts of Books
  The series manuscripts of books contains manuscript copies and drafts of books written by Angela Morgan. It is arranged chronologically. Ideas for books are also found in the Manuscripts and Drafts series (box 50).
  - The Hour Has Struck, 1914, 4 folders (Box 39)
  - The Imprisoned Splendor, 1915, 3 folders (Box 39)
  - Utterance, 1916, 3 folders (Box 39)
  - Forward March, 1918, 3 folders (Box 39)
  - Hail Man, 1919, 7 folders (Box 39)
  - Because of Beauty, 1922, 9 folders (Box 39)
  - Silver Clothes, 1926, 7 folders (Box 39)
  - Selected Poems, 1927 (Box 39)
  - Creator Man, 1929, 9 folders (Box 39)
  - Creator Man, 1929, 12 folders (Box 40)
  - Angela Morgan's Recitals, 1930, 3 folders (Box 40)
  - Heaven is Happening, 1931, 5 folders (Box 40)